Guide to the Photographer File ca. 1882-present PR 50
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
Photographer File
ca. 1882-present
PR 50
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
11.18 Linear feet (9 boxes)
The collection is a file containing photographs, mainly of New York City, taken by notable photographers.
Provenance
Most of the photographs within the Photographer File were purchased from or donated by the photographers, often for use in exhibitions. Larger gifts include the following: photographs by Alice Austen were a gift of Henry Marion Ward in 1942; Jim Beecher donated his photographs in 1986; Chris Mackay donated his photographs in 1983; Sy Edelstein donated his photographs in 1994; Wolf Von Dem Bussche's photographs were a gift of Mr. and Mrs. Timothy A. Eaton in 1997; Arthur Sacks donated his photographs in 1987; Paula Wright donated her 1964-1965 World's Fair photographs in 1993; 11 photographs by Joyce Edelman were donated by Deborah Edelman in 1992; Charles Schwartz donated photographs by a number of photographers in 2002, and Fred Rosenberg donated his photographs in 2004.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to twenty exposures of stable, unbound material per day. See guidelines in Print Room for details.
Historical Note
The Photographer File is an artificial collection of photographs that have been acquired through donation or purchase from prominent photographers. Photographs in this collection were often acquired in small numbers or for exhibitions at The New-York Historical Society. Some of the photographs in this collection were included in The New-York Historical Society exhibit "Manhattan Now: 14 Photographers Look at the Form of the City" in 1974, or the 1981 exhibit "Manhattan Observed: Fourteen Photographers Look at New York, 1972-1981." The Photographer File has developed over the years as a collection to house photographs of New York, often by well-known New York photographers. While the file consists mostly of work from the 1930s through the present, photographs by some early portrait photographers, such as Alice Boughton, Frances Benjamin Johnson, Charlotte Fairchild, Underwood & Underwood, and William A. Cooper are also included.
Scope and Content Note
The Photographer File dates primarily from 1930 through the present, but includes a few photographs by prominent photographers from as early as ca. 1882. The collection is arranged into series by size and other housing constraints; thereunder photographs are arranged alphabetically by photographer's name. Series titles refer to the box sizes; photographs within series vary in size as indicated in the folder listing. In a few instances, a photographer's work exists in a variety of sizes; notes have been provided throughout this document to guide researchers to these materials. Because of the varied nature of this collection, the photographs have been described more fully under each photographer's name in the folder listing. Researchers should be aware that in most cases the permission of the photographer is required for reproduction of images.
Included within this collection are photographs by New York Photo League photographer Arnold Eagle; New York Times fashion photographer Bill Cunningham; Magnum photographer Danny Lyon; and early female photographers Alice Austen, Alice Boughton, Margaret Bourke-White, Charlotte Fairchild, Frances Benjamin Johnson, Marie Russell, and Paula Wright. Prominent people portrayed in this collection include David Dinkins, Nelson Mandela, Albert Einstein, Doc Cheatham, Henry James, and Charles Dana Gibson.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into series by size and other housing constraints; thereunder photographs are arranged alphabetically by photographer's name
Separated Material
Photographs by the following have been removed to their own collections: Ruth Orkin (PR 190), Bill Aron (PR 192), Sidney Kerner (PR 193), Morris Huberland (PR 194), Harold Roth (PR 195), Lewis F. White (PR 196), Rhoda Galyn (PR 197), Robert Gambee (PR 198), Michael George (PR 199), David Sagarin (PR 200), Jan Staller (PR 201), Philip Trager (PR 202), Eadweard Muybridge (PR 205), William F. Winter (PR 206), and Andreas Feininger (PR 207).
Aronberg, Joseph; Austin, Alice, 1866-1952; Beecher, Jim; Bernius, Paul; Biro, Emery Reves; Boughton, Alice, 1865-1943; Bourke-White, Margaret, 1904-1971; Burckhardt, Rudy; Cheatham, Doc -- Photographs; Cherney, Lawrence; Cooper, William; Cowen, Jeff; Cunningham, William J.; Davis, Melody D., 1959-; Dinkins, David N. -- Photographs; Eagle, Arnold, 1909-1992; Edelman, Joyce Alexis, 1945-1991; Edelstein, Seymour; Einstein, Albert, 1879-1955 -- Photographs; Fairchild, Charlotte; Feinstein, Harold; Feldstein, Mark, 1937-; Fink, Peter; Garn, Andrew; Gibson, Charles Dana, 1867-1944 -- Photographs; Gottscho, Samuel H. (Samuel Herman), 1875-1971; Greenwald, Seth; Hambourg, Serge; Harmon, Steven F., 1943-; Heller, Ben; Hofer, Evelyn; Johnston, Frances Benjamin, 1864-1952; Kalmonoff, Raphael; Kent, Karen; Leifer, Martin, 1916-; Littlejohn, Ann; Lynch, Janelle; Lyon, Danny; Mackey, Chris; Mandela, Nelson, 1918- -- Photographs; Meyerhoff, Neil A., 1949-; Mikhailovich, Alexander; Nappi, Peter; Nooney, Dinanda; Roberts, Orville; Rosen, Laura; Rosenberg, Fred; Rotan, Thurman, 1903-1991; Rudnick, James; Russell, Marie Louise, 1884-1946; Sacks, Arthur; Savini, Frederico; Schiffman, Richard, 1952-; Sheer, Marcia, 1916-1989; Stroh, Eve, 1917-; Strong, Joan Vitale; Supraner, Leon, 1925-; Svennevik, Donna; Vauclaire, Gilles; Von dem Bussche, Wolf; Waters, Ray; Wright, Paula; Coasts -- New York (State); Costume -- United States; Historic buildings -- New York (State) -- New York; Marine photography; New York (N.Y.) -- Buildings, structures, etc; New York (N.Y.) -- Description and travel; Photographic prints; Portraits; Streets -- New York (State) -- New York
- Series I: 8 x 10 inches and smaller
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I is composed of photographs by the following photographers: John Albok, Jacob Aronberg, Alice Austen, Jim Beecher, William A. Cooper, John D. Earle, Serge Hambourg, Ben Heller, Evelyn Hofer, Martin Leifer, Chris Mackay, Alexander Mikhailovich, Marie Louise Russell, Eve Stroh, and the firm Underwood & Underwood
  Photographs are arranged alphabetically by photographer's name. Unless otherwise noted, one folder exists for each photographer.
  - Albok, John
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 8 x 10 in., Wash Day, view of rain falling on Madison Avenue near 96th Street. Signed., 1941 (Box 1)
  - Aronberg, Jacob
    - 2 gelatin silver prints, mounted, 3 1/4 x 4 3/4 in. of New York City urban youth. One shows the back window of a school bus with a bullet hole; the other is of a young girl in a sundress jumping rope down an urban sidewalk. Signed, dated and stamped by the photographer., 1978, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Austen, Alice (1866-1952)
    - 13 gelatin silver prints, mounted, 4 x 5 in. or smaller, of unidentified boats. (2 folders), undated (Box 1)
  - Beecher, Jim
    - 13 gelatin silver prints, 8 x 10 in., taken at the Tompkins Square Boys' Club of New York at 287 E. 10th St. in Manhattan, 1976-1986 (Box 1)
  - Cooper, William A
    - 10 gelatin silver prints, 8 x 10 in. and smaller. Unidentified portraits., undated (Box 1)
  - Earle, John D
    - 24 gelatin silver prints, 3 1/2" x 4 1/2", taken around 385 Hudson Avenue, Brooklyn, in the 1930s. Photographs are of children, many African American, playing street games, jumping rope and playing ball., [1930-1939] (Box 1)
  - Hambourg, Serge (1936-)
    - 2 color photographs of a New York subway platform and a subway entrance gate. 1 gelatin silver self-portrait, 8 x 10 in., [1970-1981] (Box 1)
      General note
      See also: Series IV
  - Heller, Ben
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 9 1/4 x 7 1/4 in., of men playing baseball in a lot in the gas house district (East 14th Street). Stamped as an Underwood & Underwood photo by Ben Heller., [1940] (Box 1)
  - Hofer, Evelyn
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 8 x 10 in., of the World Trade Center under construction., [1966-1970] (Box 1)
  - Leifer, Martin
    - 65 gelatin silver prints, 8 x 10 in. or smaller, straightforward architectural photographs of locations in Manhattan, Brooklyn, and Governors Island, including Coney Island, the Brooklyn Navy Yard, and Governors Island residences. (4 folders), 1968, 1972 (Box 1)
      See also: Series III
  - Mackay, Chris
    - 27 gelatin silver prints, 7 x 10 in., of street scenes and shop windows on the Lower East Side of Manhattan, primarily on Ludlow and Orchard Streets. (2 folders), [1970-1983] (Box 2)
  - Mikhailovich, Alexander
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 8 1/2 x 5 1/2 in., is a self portrait. 16 photomechanical views, 5 x 7 in., of New York City, including aerial views., [1990] (Box 2)
  - Russell, Marie Louise
    - 54 gelatin silver prints of New York City, various sizes, including industrial sites and harbor scenes -- unusual subject matter for a woman photographer of this era (2 folders)., [1920's-1930's] (Box 2)
  - Stroh, Eve (1917-)
    - 12 modern gelatin silver prints, 8 x 10 in., from negatives taken in the 1960s of the Essex Street market preparing for the festival of Sukkot, the demolition of the 8th Regiment Armory on 94th Street, the demolition of Pennsylvania Station, and a few views of the 1964-1965 New York World's Fair. (All were printed by Wayne Goldstein in 1983)., [1960-1969] (Box 2)
  - Underwood & Underwood (est. 1882)
    - 22 gelatin silver prints, 4 x 5 inches and smaller. Unidentified New York street scenes., [1882-1900] (Box 2)
- Series II: 11 x 14 inches
  Series II is composed of photographs by the following photographers: Emery Reves Biro, Alice Boughton, Margaret Bourke-White, Bill Cunningham, Melody D. Davis, Arnold Eagle, Seymour Edelstein, Charlotte Fairchild, Harold Feinstein, Mark Feldstein, Samuel Gottscho, Seth Greenwald, Raphael J. Kalmanoff, Ann Littlejohn, Neil Meyerhoff, Peter Nappi, Dinanda Nooney, Orville Robertson, Laura Rosen, Fred Rosenberg, James Rudnick, Richard Schiffman, Joan Vitale Strong, Donna Svennevik, Gilles Vauclaire, and Paula Wright.
  - Biro, Emery Reves (1895-1975)
    - 3 color transparencies, 8 x 10 in., 3 gelatin silver portraits, 11 x 14 in. of Biro (self portrait), Charles Dana Gibson, and Paul Lukas(?). 1 tear sheet advertisement, and 2 black and white negatives, 8 x 10 in. of unidentified women. (2 folders), undated (Box 3)
  - Boughton, Alice (1865-1943)
    - 3 palladium prints; one 7 3/4 x 4 3/4 in. portrait of Henry James, one 8 1/2 x 6 5/8 in. mounted portrait of Henry James, and one 8 x 10 in. mounted portrait of an unidentified man., 1905 (Box 3)
  - Bourke-White, Margaret (1904-1971)
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 6 3/4 x 4 1/2 in., portrait of S.J. Woolf, artist, signed by Bourke-White and a 6 1/2 x 9 1/2 inch gelatin silver print of an unidentified boat, bearing the photographer's stamp., 1943, undated (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Bill
    - 88 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in. and smaller, of models posing in front of historical buildings in appropriate period costumes, from the 1976 N-YHS exhibition "Fashion and Facades." (9 folders), [1975] (Box 3)
  - Davis, Melody D. (1959-)
    - 4 platinum/palladium prints, 12 x 10 in., of the Cathedral of St. John the Divine (Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine)., 1983 (Box 3)
  - Eagle, Arnold (1909-1992)
    - 5 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in. or smaller, of New York scenes including a high-angle interior of Pennsylvania Station, young Jews at Torah study, children playing in the street, and interiors of a Second Avenue elevated train station., [1930-1949] (Box 3)
  - Edelstein, Seymour
    - 14 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in., from Edelstein's "Shopkeepers" series. Includes portraits of Jewish shopkeepers on the Lower East Side of Manhattan and in Brooklyn. Views of storefronts, signs, and shop interiors are included., 1985-1993 (Box 3)
  - Fairchild, Charlotte
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 11 x 14 in., full length portrait of an unidentified boy and woman in front of exterior (garden?) door., undated (Box 3)
  - Feinstein, Harold
    - 7 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in. of street views, a boy writing numbers with chalk on a sidewalk, a man holding a child, and snow on tree branches. All are signed, dated and numbered., 1950-1977 (Box 3)
  - Feldstein, Mark (1937-)
    - 11 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in. of cars and architectural details of Manhattan buildings. Photographs are high-contrast with attention to form and structure., 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Gottscho, Samuel H.
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 8 1/4 x 11 in., cemetery view on Governors Island. Stamped, [1930] (Box 4)
  - Greenwald, Seth
    - 4 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in., of the George Washington Bridge from below, a woman with flyswatter, a depiction of Jesus hung beside photograph of John F. Kennedy, and girl running beside a fountain. All are signed and numbered., 1989-1995 (Box 4)
  - Kalmanoff, Raphael J.
    - 6 toned gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in., of the Coney Island Gyroscope and Steeplechase, New York street scenes, and an elevated railroad. All are signed., [1940-1949] (Box 4)
  - Littlejohn, Ann
    - 1 color photograph, 11 x 14 in., of New York Mayor David Dinkins., 1990 (Box 4)
  - Meyerhoff, Neil (1949-)
    - 5 color photographs, 11 x 14 in., of New York street life, often with reflections in shop windows., 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Nappi, Peter
    - 10 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in. of landscapes and buildings; most depict rural scenes and ruins. All are unidentified., 1989 (Box 4)
  - Nooney, Dinanda
    - 20 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in., primarily rooftop views of the West Side Highway and the Hudson River; includes a snow view., 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - Robertson, Orville (1959-)
    - 3 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in., of New York street scenes, particularly advertisements and signs. Titled, signed and dated by the photographer., 1985-1993 (Box 4)
  - Rosen, Laura
    - 1 cibachrome color prints and 5 silver gelatin prints, all 11 x 14 in., all views of or from NYC rooftops, printed for the 2001 N-YHS "Rooftops" exhibition. Views include The Yale Truck billboard and roof gardens with people sunbathing., 1980 (Box 4)
      See also Series III
  - Rosenberg, Fred
    - 15 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in., of Manhattan residents and street scenes at night, from the photographer's series "Night Gallery"., [1975] (Box 4)
  - Rudnick, James
    - 3 color prints, 11 x 14, of the Statue of Liberty renovation and cleaning. Prints made by the photographer in 2004 from his negatives. All are signed by the photographer., 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Schiffman, Richard (1952-)
    - 2 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in., one of First Calvary Cemetery in Long Island City, Queens, with the Manhattan skyline in the background, and one of the Manhattan skyline from the Queens riverfront., 1983, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Strong, Joan Vitale
    - 2 color photographs, 11 x 14 in., portraits of Nelson Mandela taken during his 1990 trip to New York. (Box 4)
  - Svennevik, Donna
    - 2 color photographs, one 8 x 10 in. and one 11 x 14 in., of New York street scenes, with green and blue stripes painted on pavement by artist Eric Arctander., [1970-1989] (Box 4)
  - Vauclair, Gilles
    - 20 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in., of New York street scenes and structures, including the Manhattan Bridge from below, Wall Street, the Pan Am Building and Grand Central Terminal, the World Trade Center, and the Woolworth Building. Also includes a view of 42nd Street and Lexington Avenue in a snow storm., 1980-1989 (Box 4)
  - Wright, Paula
    - 14 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in. and smaller. Portraits of children, pets, Albert Einstein (1946), and a self portrait. Other photographs include cows moving across the Hungarian countryside, Mexican men gathered on a stoop, and elderly farmer and his wife in the Adirondack Mountains. All are signed or initialed., 1940-1969 (Box 4)
- Series III: 16 x 20 inches
  Series III is composed of photographs by the following photographers: Lilyan Aloma, Paul Bernius, Rudy Burckhardt, Lawrence Cherney, Jeff Cowen, Peter Fink, Andrew Garn, Keith Gould, Karen Kent, Martin Leifer, Danny Lyon, Laura Rosen, Arthur Sacks, Frederico Savini, Marcia Sheer, Ray Waters, Paula Wright, and Wolf Von Dem Bussche.
  Photographs are arranged alphabetically by photographer, with the exception of Wolf Von Dem Bussche's photographs, which are housed in a custom-made metal box, at the end of the series. Unless otherwise noted, one folder exists for each photographer.
  - Aloma, Lilyan
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 16 x 20 in., of New York City buildings including a billboard, water tower and one way sign; photograph is entitled "One Way"., 2002 (Box 5)
  - Bernius, Paul
    - 1 mounted gelatin silver print, 13 1/2 x 10 1/2 in., of John Iannuzzi fleeing a fire at 572 President Street in Brooklyn, carrrying his caged parrot, Bobo; photograph is entitled Polly Wanna Cracker, Untoasted. Published newspaper clipping from the Daily News including the photograph is mounted on the verso., 1959 (Box 5)
  - Burckhardt, Rudy (1914-1999)
    - 1 black and white photomechanical print on Japanese tissue paper, 8 1/4 x 6 1/4 in., of a woman walking by the Saks & Co. storefront on 34th Street in 1938, mounted with a poem by Edwin Denby, "Mid Day Crowd"., undated (Box 5)
  - Cherney, Lawrence
    - 1 color photograph, 11 x 14 in., of S. Klein On the Square., [1970-1989] (Box 5)
  - Cowen, Jeff
    - 5 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in., of transvestite prostitutes on 14th Street in Manhattan.(2 folders), [1980-1989] (Box 5)
  - Fink, Peter
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 10 x 6 1/2 in., mounted, of a rippled reflection of an unidentified building. Mount is signed by the photographer., undated (Box 5)
  - Garn, Andrew
    - 5 color photographs, 12 x 12 in., of New York buildings, including the Guggenheim Museum, the Municipal Building, the RCA Building, 500 Fifth Avenue, and the Woolworth Building., 1981-1983 (Box 6)
  - Gould, Keith
    - 10 digital color prints, varying sizes, from 13 x 17 1/2 in. to 13 x 19 in. from his series "Subways are for Sleeping." Each print has been numbered to correspond with it's title: 1. "yellow coat," 2. "upper east side," 3. "Michelin man," 4. "nanny," 5. "pulp fiction," 6. "terror guy," 7. "serenity," 8. "yellow scarf," 9. "yankee fan," 10. "the hood.", 2006-2007 (Box 6)
  - Johnston, Frances Benjamin (1864-1952)
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 11 x 13 1/2 in., mounted, of 9 wives of the United States Cabinet, including Mrs. Daniel Scott Lamont(wife of the Secretary of War)., 1897 (Box 6)
  - Kent, Karen
    - 1 color photograph, 11 x 14 in., of the South Street seaport., 1984 (Box 6)
  - Leifer, Martin (1916-)
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 6 x 9 1/2 in., mounted, of St. Paul's Chapel with the Western Union Building., undated (Box 6)
      See also: Series I
  - Lyon, Danny (1942-)
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 7 1/2 x 7 1/2 in., of the interior of 88 Gold Street. [Plate 33 from the book "The Destruction of Lower Manhattan" (1969).] Signed, stamped, numbered, and dated on the verso., 1967 (Box 6)
  - Rosen, Laura
    - 1 cibachrome color print and 1 silver gelatin prints, both 16 x 20 in., printed for the 2001 N-YHS "Rooftops" exhibition. Photos show joggers on the roof of the McGraw Hill building, and the roof of the AT&T building, with a view of the World Trade Center., 1980-1982 (Box 6)
      See also: Series II
  - Sacks, Arthur
    - 10 gelatin silver prints, 16 x 15 in., of the 72nd Street train yards in Manhattan. (3 folders), [1974-1975] (Box 6)
  - Savini, Federico
    - 3 color prints of the Hua Mei Bird Garden in Chinatown, including views of birds and bird cages, exhibited in the 2003 N-YHS exhibition "Petropolis.", 1999 (Box 6)
  - Sheer, Marcia (1916-1989)
    - 2 cyanotypes and 3 sepia toned gelatin silver prints, 9 x 11 1/2 in. Park views, signed and labeled on verso in pencil., undated (Box 6)
  - Waters, Ray
    - 1 gelatin silver print, 10 1/2 x 13 1/2 in., mounted, of Bernard M. Baruch sitting on his favorite Central Park Bench, as a boy reads the plaque dedicating the bench to Baruch. A "Daily News" clipping of the published photograph is mounted to the verso., 1958 (Box 6)
  - Wright, Paula
    - 2 gelatin silver prints, 10 1/2 x 13 1/2 in., mounted, of New York street life. One portrays children playing street games in Harlem; the other portrays a barefoot man sleeping on a bench, covered with a newspaper with World War II headlines. Both are signed and dated by the photographer., 1944 (Box 6)
      See also: Series II and IV
  - Von Dem Bussche, Wolf
    - 10 gelatin silver prints, 16 x 20 in. Views of New York, including the World Trade Center, Washington Square, the Flatiron Building, and Foley Square housed in a custom-made metal box. Entitled "N.Y., N.Y. Ten Photographs.", 1967-1976 (Box 7)
- Series IV: 20 x 24 inches
  Series IV is composed of photographs by the following photographers: Joyce Edelman, Serge Hambourg, Stephen F. Harmon, Janelle Lynch, Alexander Mikhailovich, and Paula Wright. Also included are photographs by unidentified photographers.
  - Edelman, Joyce (1945-1991)
    - 4 gelatin silver prints, 11 x 14 in., and 7 color photographs, 16 x 20 in., of New York City. Included are street scenes, skylines, aerial views showing East River bridges, and a photograph of the New York County Supreme Court entrance at 60 Centre Street. Portraits of jazz musician Doc Cheatham are included., 1988, undated (Box 8)
  - Hambourg, Serge (1936-)
    - 1 color photograph, 16 x 20 in., of a subway platform at 34th Street and Seventh Avenue., ]1970-1979] (Box 8)
  - Harmon, Stephen F. (1943-)
    - 8 color photographs, 16 x 20 in. New York City street scenes., [1983] (Box 8)
  - Lynch, Janelle
    - 1 color photograph, 16 x 20 in., of the Hudson River by the docks of Lower Manhattan. From the photographer's series "River"., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Mikhailovich, Alexander
    - 1 double-sided photomechanical print of the Flatiron Building, hand-colored, 11 x 14 in. 1 color photograph, 16 x 20 in., of Times Square. 2 silver gelatin prints, 16 x 20 in. of New York street scenes. 2 photographic reproduction posters, 16 x 20 in., of the Manhattan skyline and an aerial view of midtown Manhattan., 1985-1993 (Box 8)
  - Unidentified
    - undated (Box 8)
  - Wright, Paula
    - 15 color slides, 2 1/4 x 2 1/4 in., of the 1964-1965 New York World's Fair including lights, people, structures and fountains. (Box 8)
      See also: Series II and III
- Series V: 24 x 30 inches
  Series V is composed of 23 gelatin silver photographic prints by Leon Supraner depicting Manhattan architecture, with a focus on structural detail. They range in size from 8 x 10 to 20 x 24 inches; most were printed by Modernage Photographic Services, Inc. for the exhibition "Manhattan Observed: Fourteen Photographers Look at New York, 1972-1981" at The New-York Historical Society in 1981.
  - Supraner, Leon (1925-)
    - 23 gelatin silver prints: 1 - 8 x 10 in., 7 - 11 x 14 in., 15 - 20 x 24 in. Structurally focused views of Manhattan architecture. One is an unattributed (self?) portrait of Supraner., [1970-1981] (Box 9)